onesmartclick.com 2014-11-30

# OneSmartClick.Com Privacy Policy Statement

Last Updated: May 15, 2009

### This is the web site of OneSmartClick.Com

We can be reached via e-mail at prashant_n_mhatre   
@ yahoo.com

### What this policy covers

  * This policy covers how OneSmartClick.Com treats your personal information. 
  * This policy doesn't cover/apply to the policies and practices of other comapnies/websites that we don't own but have been linked from our site. 

### Information Collection and Use

We don't sell your email-id. We don't spam you.

**Third Party Advertising Information:** We use Google Adsense and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

Our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

  1. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  2. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  3. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

**Do you collect IP addresses?**

Yes - web servers automatically collect IP but we do not evaluate this information for specific individuals.

### Cookies

OneSmartClick.com doesn't set or access cookies on your computer. OneSmartClick.com lets other companies who feed advertisements to us to set and access cookies on your computer.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

OneSmartClick.com may update this policy.

### Your Consent

By using this Web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to OneSmartClick.com's processing of Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes 

**Will you disclose the information you collect to outside third parties?**

NO NO NO

If you feel that this site is not following the above stated policy, you may contact us at prashant_n_mhatre   
@ yahoo.com
